One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Fight, crash in, rise up
Those are our Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go, always, don't run away
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
We're still far from our goal
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Those are our Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go, always, be the best
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
Put all our wishes together
We got to carry on Hard knock days
A Man's World
Team Kin'emon
Executive tower Junkyard
Somebody was in the wall?!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Kanjuro!
Oh, Kin'emon!
This is great!
Really!
I'm sorry. I think I made you search for me a bit.
Some strange things happened one after another...
so I was planning to hide myself in the wall for a while.
A samurai from the Wano Country
Evening Shower Kanjuro
But I fell asleep before I knew it.
Anyway, Kin'emon,
I can't believe you came back!
Sorry to keep you waiting for so long!
I trusted you so I didn't mind even a bit.
Don't be so stiff and formal, friend.
With my sorcery,
I didn't have a problem getting food.
Oh well, I'm not hungry at all but...
Want some lettuce?
No, I don't.
Your food never agrees with my stomach.
Well, as long as
you and Momonosuke are okay...
Yes, we are, thanks to you!
Good. I hope I can see Momonosuke soon.
Yeah, Momonosuke is looking forward to seeing you, too!
So many things happened since I last saw you, but I can't put it in a nutshell!
We have a lot to talk about!
I'll tell you later!
Okay, got it! Let's get out of here!
Get out?
Is there a way to get out of here?
Is he...?
Drawing something?
Come on out!
Spring Sparrow!
What?!
No way!
His drawing started moving!
Is he a Devil Fruit eater?
That picture of a bird came to life!
But the drawing is terrible...
His ability is amazing,
but because of his drawing skills, that sparrow doesn't seem to be too good at flying...
Now, Kin'emon, let's go!
Uh-huh.
Wait a sec!
We're former King Riku army soldiers and citizens that had been living as toys...
We don't know what's going on
but is King Riku alright?!
Our families are in the town!
Take us out with you! I beg you!
Colosseum Army Royal Palace 4th level 3rd level 2nd level 1st level
Stop Straw Hat and the others!
Why don't you aim at us?!
Guillotine High-Heel!
Oh, the Longleg got beat!
Don't look away, Straw Hat!
We must get to the Palace wher Doflamingo is, at any cost!
I knew it when I heard Doflamingo's speech!
It's a game to kill me.
Kill or get killed.
Everyone in this country will become hunters!
The only way for you to survive is...
...to kill somebody!
This game called the Birdcage is all fake!
As soon as the weapon trafficking and the secret with the toys were revealed,
all the people currently in this country were sentenced to extermination, I think.
Doflamingo won't let any information out of the country.
That's why he enclosed the island in the Birdcage.
Which means right now Dressrosa is...
...a solitary island, cut off from the rest of the world!
Believing in miracles and waiting for the end of the game will get us all killed!
The only way to get out of this island alive is to move forward and kill Doflamingo.
There are a variety of troubles in this country...
So many unexpected things are happening around him
but it seems Doflamingo is enjoying it.
I don't know anyone who's more cunning than Doflamingo.
Doflamingo is a notch above all the others on all fronts but he made just one mistake!
He brought in all those odd, tough warriors from all over the world for the event at the Colosseum.
We're not gonna be defeated!
Because, after all, I will take down Doflamingo!
What are you talking about?!
I said I'm gonna kick Mingo's ass!
I said it would be me, Straw Hat-ya!
I'm very impressed, but I'm gonna do it!
Soldier! You said you wanna kill one of the Executives!
That's a personal thing!
Taking back King Riku's country is my inevitable duty!
I have to put an end to the tragedy that started 10 years ago!
If you talk about time, I have a grudge from 13 years ago!
Then, mine's from 30 years ago!
Don't lie! There's no way that you're older than me!
You guys, get off!
You get off!
The road's ending!
Almost there! The third level!
All right!
Go straight to the fourth level like this!
Horse!
What are those giant dolls?!
On top of the
Pica statue
Zoro vs. Pica
How could you even think you were good enough to kill Straw Hat?
You bastard!
Damn!
I guess he got away!
Pulpostone!
What?!
Why're you guys flying?!
Zo-!
Z-Z-Z-Z-Zoro-senpai!
Oh! D-Do you remember you promised me your autograph?!
That's... Pica!
Rebecca!
Who is it?
He's one of the Top Executives of the Donquixote Family along with Trebol and Diamante!
Zoro! Keep the enemy there for us!
We have to move beyond this stone figure!
Current Location
Flower Field
I can do that but...
That aside, why're you guys flying...?
Oh? The enemy got away, didn't he?!
No, he didn't get away!
I won't let you get to the Palace!
He got in there...
What?!
H-He's targeting us!
Oh yeah! Your barrier!
I can't put up a barrier that can cover us from that massive punch!
No! But if nothing is done, we're gonna...
...get blown away!
Three-Sword Style!
Thousand-and-Eighty Pound Phoenix!
I'm starting to see how your power works!
I forgot to tell you one thing.
The Straw Hats are...
...not just Straw Hat Luffy and God Usopp.
Don't forget!
I'm the man who's destined to become the greatest swordsman in the world one day!
Zoro-senpai!
Further beneath the
Trading port
Executive tower
Scrap Heap
Awesome!
Thank you, samurai!
We can get out from here finally!
Take turns climbing out!
Since it's a pictorial ladder, it breaks easily!
The lines aren't straight so it's hard to climb!
Stop complaining!
You've got a lot of nerve!
Inside the SMILE Factory
The Little People are going crazy!
Keep them down!
It's no good!
We can't get control of them!
Don't give up! Keep shooting!
We're not gonna get hit by bad people's bullets!
W-Wait! Aren't you worried about Princess Mansherry?!
What?
If you guys get out of here, Princess Mansherry will never get cured!
Th-That's not good!
No! Don't listen to them, Chao!
Okay, if you understand, quit fighting and just obey us...
What?!
I put in earplugs so I can't hear your stupid lies anymore!
Tontatta Swing!
Report Young Master-sama!
O-Okay!
You can't do that!
Tontatta Tail...
Four-man Hammer!
Everybody! Release all their Transponder Snails into the wild so they can't call for backup!
Are you listening?!
What?
Earplugs!
Princess' Aide
Mouji
It's good that her illness was a lie!
But she's been alone all this time in the factory...
I understand!
Mouji... I Mouji understand your feelings!
Wait!
I know the princess is crying now!
She's crying and calling my name!
Huh?
Mouji!
There is the isolation ward!
Princess Mansherry must be in there!
I'm gonna save you now!
Oh, wait a second!
Why did you stop me?!
Look at that sign!
It says "Keep out"! We can't go in!
What?! You should've told me earlier!
I can't slow down now!
Mouji broke the door with the "Keep out" sign!
I'm disappointed in you!
It means you're not allowed to go in without permission!
I'm sorry...
No one's in here! Is it just storage?
Are you ready?!
Here we go!
Hurry up!
In front of the SMILE factory
Oh! You're so relentless, Senor!
Almost!
Franky Ear.
Franky was born with good hearing.
Hey, swimming guy...
It's none of your concern but...
...earlier...
I saw a weak old granny having trouble in the back street on the right...
Oh yeah? That's sad.
Turn the wheel and open the door!
Hold on! Shrimps!
SMILE Factory manager
Kuween (20 years old, female)
You're pushing your luck!
I won't let you get out!
No! It's the factory manager!
You guys were slaves for manufacturing SMILEs right from the start!
Didn't you notice until now?!
Stop making a ruckus like fools!
If nothing is done, we're all gonna get caught!
Open the door already!
Well done. Guys!
It's a robot!
A robot came to save us!
Thank you!
A robot!
Cool!
Is everybody okay?!
How are you?!
We all came to save you!
To save... us?
I-I'm so happy for all of you!
Thank you, Robot-san!
His not a Robot!
He's our savior, a Big Human - Fraland!
A Big Human?!
What kind of person is Princess Mansherry?
Princess Mansherry is...
You fools!
How dare you pay no notice to me for such a long time!
The factory
is
my life!
I'm the factory manager.
I'm the most powerful figure in this factory!
You're Cyborg Franky of the Straw Hats, aren't you?
You're a One-star criminal.
How did you make it this far alive?
What did you do to Pink-sama?
That fool?
Anyway, I won't let you do as you like in this factory!
I'm gonna take your life!
Watch out! Run, Fraland!
Fraland hugged the factory manager!
H-Hey, what's going on?!
What are you doing?! Let go of me!
Did Fraland fall in love with her?!
That cyborg idiot, how dare he fool me!
There's no troubled old granny anywhere.
Well, I'm relieved to know that.
Oh! So hard-boiled!
Senor Pink! I'm ready! Bring it on anytime!
Hey, stop messing with
the morals in the factory!
That bastard has been throwing me around with suplexes!
Was he trying to dig up a hot spring or something
with the back of my head?!
What are you talking about?!
Drop dead!
Cat-Ear Punch!
Franky Southland Suplex!
No! The manager is...
That hurt, you jerk!
How could you use my head like a hammer?!
How dare you treat me so cruelly!
I'm the factory manager!
I'm the most powerful figure here!
Once she gets mad, nobody can stop her!
Please run, Fraland!
I'll cut up your body and suck your guts up with my vacuum then pound them into pieces!
Why don't you cry like a baby, you...
Fraland kissed the factory manager!
H-He kissed...
This guy just stole a kiss from me...
Now, get up, you swimming idiot!
H-Hey!
Wait a minute! What are you thinking?!
Why did you do that?!
B-Be a man about it and become my boyfriend!
You fool!
The manager just became a bit more feminine...
You can't blame him, factory manager.
What?
You got involved. It's your fault.
Pink-sama! But...
You cut in to a fight between grown men.
When a woman does that, how else can we seal her mouth?
Getting upset over a kiss or two makes you just an immature little tramp.
So don't talk about love or relationships or that sort of stuff!
That's right.
Love with a little chick like that...
...Would drive me nuts!
So hard-boiled!
Senor! Franky!
How hard-boiled you two are!
I won't let you destroy the factory!
Prove it with your fists! If you're a man!
It's gonna start! The men's fight!
Diaper Bombs!
Nipple Light Special!
In front of the royal palace plateau
Pica statue
Are you giving up on hiding in the stone?
How dare you let Rebecca and the others get away!
Thank you!
I couldn't have done it without you.
Don't think shitheads like you guys can escape this country!
We're almost there at the second level!
Be careful where you land!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Hello, this is Leo.
It's Mouji!
Mouji! I'm glad to hear from you!
That means our friends have been released!
But Leo, we have a big problem...
What is it?
The princess is...
Princess Mansherry is...
...nowhere to be found in the factory!
What?!
The poor dear...
She must be locked up somewhere and crying "Mouji! Mouji!"
No...
Get to the old King's Plateau!
Yeah!!
Catch King Riku and God Usopp!
Former King's Plateau
N-No need to be afraid.
They can't climb up here that easily...
Kill God Usopp!
Father-sama, I just got a call from the Tontattas in the factory!
Oh, are they alright?!
Yes.
But they told me they can't find Princess Mansherry anywhere.
What?!
What are you guys talking about?!
Everyone in this country is looking for us!
Let's run now!
Where are you gonna go when everyone in this country is looking for you?
It'll be fine.
They know the truth about the past.
They're not gonna harm Father-sama.
What about me?
If they're hiding Princess Mansherry elsewhere, it must be in the Palace.
She must be somewhere.
Search every nook and cranny.
I don't think Doflamingo has killed Mansherry.
I know he needs her ability.
Though we need that ability more than him now...
Royal Palace
A Certain Room
Here. Your food.
I want to go back to Green Bit!
Come and save me now!
Leo!